(Leonard:)if you were attached
to another object
(Leonard:)by an inclined plane wrapped
helically around an axis?
(Sheldon:)Screwed.
(Leonard:)There you go.
(Sheldon:)Amy's right.
(Sheldon:)He is tedious.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, get the door!
(Howard(off):)Why can't you get it?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
You know I'm doing a bowel cleanse
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)for my colonoscopy!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I'm like an upside-down
volcano here.
(Howard:)Oh, hey.
(Howard:)I hope you didn't hear that.
(Leonard:)The volcano thing? No.
(Howard:)What's with the T-shirt?
(Howard:)You working at the
Apple store now?
(Leonard:)No, it's just something
I threw on.
(Howard:)I know all your shirts.
(Howard:)That's not one of them...
(Howard:)You were pretending to
work at the Genius Bar
(Howard:)to pick up women,
weren't you?